Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-246
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- AFL (American Federation of Labor) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: AFL and CIO hookup?, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Newspaper clipping.
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: AFL renews bid for labor merger, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: City employees map legislative fight for new benefits, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Get tough policy is urged by AFL, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Green and Murray rebuke Congress for price 'record', 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: High court rules non-red oaths apply to 'parent' labor unit heads, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Labor in Seattle protests MacArthur visit as 'political', 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Labor unification hinted by Murray, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: New world union maps war on Reds, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Organized labor offers proposals to help fight against inflation, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Pay curbs fought in prices are free, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Spaniard favors AFL-CIO visit, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Talk of a third union federation, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Tobin reassures 'free' worker, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: US labor intercedes for Bolivian miners, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: US labor to omit Yugoslav parley, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Visit of McArthur met by protests, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Labor edges toward the GOP, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: 3 members defend wage body set-up, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: 500 lawyers employed by US labor movement, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: AFL and CIO groups indorse school bonds, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Address before the AFL Convention at Philadelphia, PA, Dec. 1892, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: John Swinton
  - Item 23: Address before the American Federation of Labor Convention at Philadelphia, Pa., Dec., 1892, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Address by Edward F. McGrady, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Edward F. McGrady
  - Item 25: Address delivered at the American Federation of Labor Convention, at Philadelphia, Pa., 1892, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry W. Blair
  - Item 26: Addresses all too brief to catalog, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: American Federation of Labor
  - Item 27: Labor and education: address delivered before the 57th Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, Denver, Colorado, on October 6, 1937, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Spencer Miller
  - Item 28: Labor seeks life more abundantly, 1925; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: William Green
  - Item 29: Labor, democracy and fascism: from proceedings of the 54th annual convention of the American Federation of Labor at San Francisco, Oct. 1-12, 1934, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Labour and the war, an address to the American federation of labour, 1942 convention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: William Lyon Mackenzie King
  - Item 31: Letter - Official communication between Mr. M.L. Hoffman and William Green of A.F.L., 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Management and Labor - their common interestaddress by Matthew Woll (Press release), 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Matthew Woll
  - Item 33: President Green extols labor movement as shield of democracy and relentless foe of dictatorships, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Social obligations of business, industry and labor, 1931; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Speech delivered by John Mitchell at the Toronto Convention., 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: John Mitchell
  - Item 36: Speech of Frank P. Walsh of Kansas City, Missouri, before 34th Annual Convention, AFL, 1914; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Frank P. Walsh
  - Item 37: Speech to the Seventieth Convention of the AFL in San Francisco, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Nelson H. Cruikshank
  - Item 38: Taxation and labor, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: The last five years, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: George Meany
  - Item 40: The relations of labor to National Defense, 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry Lewis Stimson
  - Item 41: The Union or Non-Union shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Frank Morrison
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Educators demand new labor party, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Europe's frantic arms race, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Green exposes 'school-freedom' plea in Brookwood College..., 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Labor leaders urge Roosevelt, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Labor party here opposed by Green, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Morrison makes radio talk, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: New miracles of chemistry, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Organized labor stands pat, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Power of courts assailed by Green, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: PWA purchases gave jobs, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Tighe gives up union to Lewis..., 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Unions employers sued as plotters, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: A momentous day for the army of labor, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: AFL lays plans to war on critics, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: AFL to vote on immigration ban, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Check off plan of unions held legal..., 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Labor is warned on aid from laws, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Labor planks submitted by AFL to the Republican National Convention, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Motor magnates pay themselves big salaries.., 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Socialist advise a new Lewis party, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Solving America's race problem, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: A case of arbitration, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: AFL and CIO denounce US for abstaining on Tunisian case, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: AFL and CIO in politics go together separately, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: AFL and CIO try to select leaders, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Both AFL and CIO set to name new presidents - merger talk is revived, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: CIO and AFL men fight with knives, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Customs men eye union affiliation, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Farm labor blocs opposed to UMT, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Labor faces election in an uncertain mood, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: Labor farm units back foreign aid, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Labor leaders bid union members win 'liberal' congress in Nov., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Labor turns down Barkley as too old, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Labor's aid grows in welfare work, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Major test snaps AFL-CIO peace, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Move to reduce funeral costs by a union co-operative is begun, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Rival labor chiefs map Chicago plans, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Sitdown Strike laid to US aides, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: Truman and Stevenson, bid for the labor vote, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: Union press for federal health benefits, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: Union split bogs Taft Act change, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: Unions ask review of picket decision, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Unions told to win 'liberal' congress, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: Worst invasion by gangsters since '33 vexes unions here, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 45: CIO acts to bar defections to AFL, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 46: The new labor leaders a dual portrait, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: AFL adopts industrial unionism, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 48: AFL chiefs say new deal leads to ruin, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 49: AFL position on vertical unions, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: AFL to urge 30-hour week, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 51: American churches appeal for square deal to labor, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 52: Churches issue labor message, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: AFL council asks CIO to discuss merger, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: AFL declares restrictive curbs must not be imposed on labor, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: AFL sues to block new wire process, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Expect little change in union picture for cosmetic firms, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Green warns against passage of labor curbs, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Lead of AFL in south is seen as temp, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Luxury taxes repeal asked by AFL, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Steps to bar paralyzing strikes pressed by leaders in Congress, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: US to discuss AFL protest over Germany, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: AFL forms a committee to back Truman, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: AFL stiffens drive on Reds in Canada, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: GOP weighing views of labor, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: 50,000 parade might of labor, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: AFL and CIO urge heavier profits tax than 4 billion Truman requests, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: AFL gains 13,000 in railroad voting, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: AFL, CIO protest on arms to Arabs, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: AFL, CIO to aid police, firemen, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Candidates defies 'threat' of labor, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: CIO, AFL indorse day's pay gift to community chest, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: City relief study assigned to labor, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Connecticut labor unites for Bowles, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Co-op plan killed by house in voting for 'middle' homes, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Green and Murray to aid fund drive, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Jobless pay seen a political issue, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Labor displease with Democratic line up in state, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Labor groups plan drives to get registrants to polls Tuesday, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Labor joins fight on Marcantonio, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Labor men talk unity action yet to come, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Labor move a help for impellitteri..., 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Picket slow DPW trucks, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Strike threatens industry stoppage, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Tobin and unions cheerful on 1950, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Union groups join to bar relief cut, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: Union heads join to aid Red Cross, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Union merger to be delayed, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Unity move in labor faces many obstacles, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: US labor opposes aid to Argentina, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: AFL, CIO unite for Taft's defeat, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Labor paraders hear Governor, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: Profits and bosses, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: AFL asks top role in new world hunt, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Green is doubtful of Taft Act repeal, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Taft accuses AFL of greatest claim for special status, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The consistent Mr. Green, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: AFL seen friendly to new labor bill, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: AFL survey urge orderly price.., 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: AFL and CIO negotiators set final stage for December..., 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: AFL and CIO to unite today, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: AFL and CIO will merge, ending 20-year labor split, Meany will head new body, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: AFL takes step without fanfare, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: AFL unanimous for union merger, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: AFL-CIO a harmonious beginning, but, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: AFL-CIO its official now, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: AFL-CIO leader completes 4 standing committees, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: AFL-CIO merger slated in Canada, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: AFL-CIO merger smiles hide scars of former battles, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: AFL-CIO merger stirs labor monopoly charge, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Arabella scenes on disks..., 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Armory crowned by labor meeting, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Author of labor split in 1936..., 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Big Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Challenged labor leader, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: CIO body backs labor unity plan, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: CIO Executive Board approves merger with AFL next week, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: CIO head urges change for 1956, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: CIO-AFL to seek more office unions, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: City may be site of labor merger, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Cleric terms AFL the 'bride' offers 'marital' advice to unions', 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Construction unions may use welfare fund to rebuild city slums, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Doubts on unity voiced in AFL, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Eisenhower hears union wage plea, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Eisenhower's talk excerpts from Meany and Reuther speeches, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Enlightened labor unionism, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Harriman attack on GOP bids for AFL-CIO favor, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Harriman scores Eisenhower aides as foes of labor, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: History of labor movement in Country, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Independent unions face effort by mergered union, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Industrial unit of labor set up, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Joint labor eyes role in 1956 race, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: Labor and management debate what each wants from other, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 41: Labor and NAM speak, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: Labor and politics, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 43: Labor delegates attend church, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 44: Labor joins up, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 45: Labor merger likely to spur organizing, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 46: Labor slate widened, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 47: Labor to remain on Mitchell unit, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 48: Labor unity abroad, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 49: Labor urges ban on funds, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 50: Labor will begin organizing drive, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)